Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was harmed
during the filming.
My wives...
who devoted themselves to
Kızıl Elma...
and risk their lives
when needed.
My brother.
We overcome all the schemes
of the heathens.
All the weapons they drew,
cut them first.
Thank Allah, we have the children,
the future of our tribe.
And the ones who attempted to burn
Söğüt are burned to ashes.
We hit them with the move
they made against us.
Now, it's our turn.
Now is the time for conquest.
Our first objective is İnegöl!
To break those walls down,
we need catapults.
And we need weapons to arm
our alps.
And for that, we need iron.
The way to the castle is full
of mines.
There are iron mines in İnegöl.
If we take it, then we'll solve
our problem.
We need to calculate it, Osman Bey.
Are the mines effective?
How many men are protecting them?
The iron is known by
the smith, brother.
Master Davud is already in İnegöl
in disguise.
Mashallah. It's a good move, Osman Bey.
Wise one.
-Inshallah, he'll return with good news.
-Inshallah.
Inshallah, he'll return.
Governor Saguros left İznik to
meet us.
We'll host him according to
the Turkish customs.
-Are the preparations done?
-Everything is ready, my bey.
İznik will talk about our
hospitality for days, my bey.
We show our hospitality to
those who come as friends.
And we teach the ones who come
as enemies on the battlefield.
Now, sharpen your swords.
The time for conquest is soon.
New miners are coming.
We'll infiltrate with them.
Blend with the crowd.
Don't get attention.
I don't want trouble, alps.
We'll infiltrate, Master Davud.
Come on!
They even stop the villagers
passing through.
The heathens are protecting it well.
Go on.
It's the same on the rear.
It's full of archers.
They chose a good position.
They protect it.
They are here. Scouting first,
conquest later.
Come on, alps.
May Allah help us.
Move, move!
Move!
-It's Marcus.
-He doesn't know us.
If he does, we are dead.
But we are taking him with us.
The end is martyrdom.
What are you talking about there?
Move!
Move! Move!
Do you really consider marrying
Nikola, my lady?
This marriage won't happen, Cornelia.
Love is as strong as death.
How different is spending a life
with someone you don't love than dying?
I will never marry him.
You didn't forget what we talked
about, right?
You need to finish your preperations
for marriage.
By the way, you left the castle
yesterday without telling me.
Where did you go?
I took some fresh air.
I didn't go far, brother.
I was at Harmankaya.
You are lying to my face!
How can you go to Turgut's tribe
without telling me?
-What are you up to, Mari?
-It's none of your business, brother!
Arrogant!
You won't step out of this castle
before marrying Nikola.
Have you heard me?
My eyes are on you!
This marriage will happen tomorrow!
My lady!
My lady, are you alright?
My brother thinks that he can use
me as a pawn. But he is wrong!
I want you to do something
for me, Cornelia.
-This is important for me.
-There is nothing I won't do for you.
Go to Turgut and ask for his help.
He should kidnap me before
marrying Nikola.
Do you trust him that much?
I trust him more than anyone right now.
The mine is right here, my bey.
The mine is close to the castle.
Whateve happens...
we'll take that mine.
Tell me, Master Davud.
The seam of the mine is
efficient.
This means a lots of weapons
for our alps!
If we take that mine, my bey...
I can make the sharpest
arrowheads.
I can make the strongest balls
that will pierce the walls.
Everything that we need
is in this mine.
The mine is so fertile that...
we can even trade with the
weapons I will forge.
Mashallah, Master Davud.
We didn't send the master there
for nothing.
The iron that meets your forge
will surely become a weapon.
But it's difficult, my bey.
We need to pass the İnegöl borders.
May God forgive Priest Gregor's
sins.
He had only one job!
Only one job!
Placing the flying fire!
He couldn't even do that!
His God can forgive him if
he wants, I won't!
Priest Gregor was my friend! Watch your
words when you speak his name!
-He died fighting for our cause!
-What happened has happened.
You won't fight for a dead priest,
will you?
İznik's governor, Saguros.
Governor Saguros.
What a pleasent surprise.
We didn't expect you.
I didn't come here for a visit,
but to warn you.
-About what?
About the attack on Osman Bey
on the Nikea Road!
Osman is our enemy.
Don't be arrogant, Kosses!
They tried to poison him in my castle!
The attackers on the road keep
attacking in my palace.
I attacked Osman!
I would do it again!
You are the one who trades with Osman...
faces us and shadows the cross!
After all, me and my friends...
we know not to trust
the Turks.
What about you, Saguros?
How do you know that Osman
didn't poison you?
Look, he became a hero
in your eyes...
and a friend at your side.
You are a babbler, Nikola.
The tongue might be the end of
many powerful people.
Saguros...
even the strongest men...
get vanished in these times...
like little flies...
and I'm not the one
talking carelessly.
It's you.
And also, it's you who
united with Osman...
and betrayed us.
Lords!
I'm Saguros...
the governor of Nikea!
I'm going to visit Kayı Tribe.
Osman Bey will protect my
caravans...
and my goods.
And you will accept it...
either easily or hardly.
This is my last word.
Every throne is slippery...
in these lands, Saguros.
Be careful.
Farewell.
What do you think, my bey?
How will we pass the İnegöl border?
There is a solution for every trouble.
I didn't invite Governor Saguros
for nothing, Master Davud.
We'll enter İnegöl
with his caravan.
The mine isn't just for weapons.
For the conquest of the İnegöl,
we must surround it first.
We'll work on it piece by piece.
When the time comes,
they all will appear.
Having Saguros on our side will
make the lords divide.
This...
will benefit us.
May I enter...
Aygül Hatun?
Look, I'm coming in?
Mad girl?
Where are you?
No?
Where are you mad girl?
-What's wrong with your face?
-I'm coming from a mission.
Did you forget your tent?
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for you.
I'll return to my mission in the morning.
I wanted to see you.
I came to see you.
In mine, when I was
working in the darkness...
I saw this stone.
It glowed in the darkness.
It reminded me of you.
You enlighten my darkness...
just like this stone.
Cerkutay.
Say yes, girl!
Isn't it enough waiting?
-Move, Cerkutay!
-Say yes to me!
-No, I won't
-You won't?
-Come on!
-I hope the mine falls on my head!
And you will feel guilty.
-You will wish you said yes.
-I won't, Cerkutay. I won't.
You soiled everywhere!
Move!
-You will regret it?
-I won't!
I'm going!
I'm gone!
Crazy.
Crazy man.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come.
What's wrong, Cornelia?
What are you doing here?
-Nothing bad happened, right?
-Turgut Bey. I brought news from Mari.
I'm listening.
Lord Kosses.
He wants to force her to marry Nikola.
Nikola.
-When is this wedding?
-Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
What's this hurry?
Are they running away from a fire?
I don't know, sir.
What does she want from me?
To save her.
No one else can help her.
Will you save her?
Firstly, I want to know something.
Your lady, Mari, why does she
trust me?
You can ask her personally
when you save her.
Good. Go, then. I'll give my answer.
Alright, sir.
If you allow me.
Serhan, accompany Cornelia
on the way.
Look at this nomad Osman!
He swayed Governor Saguros to his
side. He wants to break our unity!
We are closer than ever.
We know what to do.
We can't let him hurt us.
Saguros will die like a fly!
If that Saguros...
dies as Osman's guest...
the Emperor will send a great
army after Osman.
Only the Emperor?
When Osman went to collide
with Nikea...
I talked to Seljuk vizier Alemşah.
He doesn't like Osman's growth.
Alemşah will go after Osman who's
acting on his own.
Then, we should do our
part too.
Julia, this is a job for
your men.
As you order, lord Lagotus.
Julia.
You'll bring your men to me.
Not only Saguros...
his daughter will die too.
I want a great tragedy.
Alps!
Attention!
Welcome.
Thank you.
Welcome!
Come.
Alps!
Come on!
Mashallah!
To be honest, I didn't expect
such a mighty greeting.
Respect to the guest...
comes from the glory
of the beylig.
You didn't see anything yet.
Watch the archery drill of the alps.
Alps!
Arrows!
Get ready!
Release!
Turks!
None can beat you at archery.
It's just what we heard.
Even more.
My daughter Hera.
She wanted to meet you and see
your tribe.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
We couldn't see you at İznik, Hera.
You did well by coming.
I was in Constantinople then.
I'm glad to meet you even if
it's late.
My daughter, if you are curious about
our tribe...
let us show you around.
What do you say?
I would like that.
Then, let's get to the tent.
Let us pass the time of the day.
Gladly, Osman Bey.
Come.
Alright then, come.
Turgut Bey' Tribe
We'll help Mari.
But we can't enter the castle.
We'll kidnap her on the way.
My bey, you say well but...
what if it's a trap?
Mari trusted me and asked
for help.
It doesn't fit us to not hold
the hand that asks for help.
Take your cautions and
ready the alps.
And inform Cornelia personally.
Tomorrow, on the İnegöl road...
we'll kidnap Mari.
As you order, my bey.
For you.
I thought it would fit a bey like you.
Thank you, Mari.
What do you think about the Latins
invading Constantinople?
Years passed after the destruction
of the Catholic Latins.
But the signs of it can still be seen In
Constantinople.
What can I think about it?
But everything is well in Constantinople.
With overseas trade and
goods coming from the west...
they live in prosperity.
But...
I hear that some people in Constantinople
want to unite with the Catholics.
Is it wrong?
Fools who lost their memory
can think that.
But that's not what the
majority thinks, Osman Bey.
So, they should've realized that...
the crusades hurt them
before anyone else.
How are things in Seljuks?
We hear that they are oppressed by
the Mongols in Konya.
They reign.
When is it ever seen that those
who stand up against Turks lived forever?
They won't live long either.
Sultan Mesut's resistance is
important for us too.
He is a wall between us and the Mongols.
May God be with them
against the Mongols.
Thank you.
Allah is with those who
have faith.
Surely, the enemies have
a common end.
Ya hak!
Boran.
Swing it!
Alps!
This is easy for Göktuğ.
Swing it harder.
Swing it!
Can you shoot this well?
Come on, girls!
Show her.
Come on.
Mashallah.
Ya hak!
Mashallah to my daughters.
Amazing.
Swing it!
We'll eat dinner at Söğüt.
Before it we can see...
the goods and manufactories
that brought you here.
I really want to see that.
I'm so happy to trade with you, Osman Bey.
This trade will strengthen you and
Nikea.
Inshallah.
How can that happen?
Do you have a secret?
The secret is here, my girl.
But we have another secret.
We are nomads.
And while moving we always
look for trouble.
So, we train our children
when they are little.
Without discriminating by gender.
Now let's see how you do it.
Come on.
Come on, try it.
I knew that would happen.
I can't do it.
I'm not as good as you.
Göktuğ!
Come here.
-Yes, mother.
-Come.
Look, my daughter.
This is Göktuğ.
He is a talented archer.
He can teach you how to
shoot arrows.
Not at all, mother.
I can share what I know.
You are, son.
You are a good archer.
Talent deserves admiration.
Teach her well how to do it.
When your drill ends, you can
bring our guest back.
Alright, mother.
Ladies, would you like to drink
something?
Come on, there are things to
do in the tent.
Come on. To our jobs!
The girl is pretty.
And single.
Listen to your mother Selcan and
don't miss that.
Mother.
Don't blush, son.
Don't blush.
They are your sisters,
not strangers.
Go on.
You don't miss anything, mother.
Looking is for the eyes, my daughter.
Seeing is for the heart.
Firstly, we'll wear this ring.
Come.
You'll stand like this.
Take your arrow...
look at your target...
draw your bow...
Amazing!
Will I be able to shoot this good?
Of course, if you train well,
you will be a good archer.
Come on, try it.
Draw it.
Hold it a little above.
Look at your target,
draw your bow.
Just like this.
Saguros and his daughter will die.
I don't want any mistake.
You'll do what's needed.
Governor Saguros...
and his daughter won't leave
Söğüt alive.
And the responsible...
will be Osman.
May I enter, mother.
Come, son.
You summoned me.
Come, come.
Sit here.
Tell me.
How was it?
Did you teach her well?
Was she a good teacher?
She learned, mother.
She learned.
She is talented.
You wouldn't call her a Rum girl.
It's apparent.
She is talented.
She shot the target.
Wait, mother.
Don't make me shy.
There is no shyness in love, son.
You open your chest against
spears and swords...
are you afraid of love?
There are possible things and
impossible things, mother.
She is the governor's daughter.
I'm an alps with nothing else
but his sword.
How can I compete.
If I dream for impossible,
I can't be happy.
What is impossible?
You have a heart.
Don't we all pray to Allah
who is all capable, Göktuğ?
Huh?
Only he holds the hearts.
If he wrote it, no one can
erase it.
And if she is the governor's daughter...
you are Osman Bey's
lion alp.
Huh?
If the love is in your heart,
you won't give up.
I will tell your Osman Bey.
We'll go and ask for Hera.
Alright, my lion?
Really, mother?
Do you think the governor will
accept it?
Wouldn't he? After Osman Bey asks?
But, you should make
sure of the girl's heart first.
Thank you, mother.
-Thank you.
-You too, son.
You too.
Harmankaya Castle
-Stop, what are you doing?
-It's me, Serhan.
We'll kidnap Mari on
the İnegöl Road.
Thank God.
My lady will be so happy.
I'm grateful.
Söğüt
Welcome, my bey!
Thank you!
Good day!
May your business prosper.
Allah bless you, my bey.
I didn't know that you Turks
urbanized like this.
You must've put in some real effort.
We'll urbanize even more, inshallah.
It's all for the prosperity
of the people.
Welcome, Selcan Hatun!
Salam Alaikum.
-Good day.
-Welcome, my lady.
Look.
You will like Söğüt.
It seems like.
It's the craft of our women. They
make it from madder.
Is that so?
It's really pretty.
Let it be a memento.
I'm grateful, Bala Hatun.
Thank you.
I'll always keep it.
Come on.
May Allah prosper you.
Come, my girl.
Come.
-Welcome, Osman Bey!
-Thank you.
Thank you.
My sheik!
My sheik Edebali!
-Governor Saguros.
-Welcome, Governor Saguros.
Thank you.
Wait.
Not now.
Wait for him to separate
from Osman.
Our target is Saguros.
Salam Alaikum.
And Alaikum Salam.
Alaikum Salam.
Yes, Turgut Bey.
There is something important, Osman Bey.
Of course, if you have time.
Then, let's speak at the inn.
Did you sleep well, Nikola?
No.
Not at all.
I thought about Saguros until
morning.
I thought about what will happen
to Osman when he dies.
Don't worry, Nikola.
Our plan will succeed this time.
Don't worry.
Do you know why else I couldn't
sleep?
Mari.
You still haven't told me anything.
Have you talked to Mari, Kosses.
I'm afraid, you'll have to convince
her personally, Nikola.
You are right.
When Mari sees how much I value her...
after seeing the gifts I bring her...
without a doubt.
Any good news?
Turgut Bey will save you at the
İnegöl Road.
Dear Mari.
Welcome.
I should leave you alone.
I hope you'll make the right
decision.
I'm sorry, Mari.
I should've come to you first
for such a delicate matter.
Forgive me.
If you say yes to me...
everything I own will be yours.
The greatest...
the greatest gift that I can
give you...
aren't these.
I offer you...
endless happiness.
Mari with pretty eyes.
Will you marry me?
When you marry me...
what will change in your life, Nikola?
Many things.
Our loyalty to each other will
make us much more stronger.
Loyalty and power.
Is it enough for a marriage?
Of course not.
Amor, Mari.
Amor.
Love.
Belive me, Mari.
Even a fire without love
is in darkness.
And I, Aya Nikola,
promise you...
we'll never be in darkness
for a second in our lives.
I promise you.
I hope so, Nikola.
We'll be so strong and
so happy, Mari.
You will never regret it.
Never.
Mari informed me.
I didn't know what to do.
I wanted to ask you.
His brother Kosses. Even though
she doesn't want it...
he is forcing her to
marry Nikola.
What does she want from you?
To save her.
It's the customs of the Turks.
Those who need help get
helped.
I will kidnap Mari, Osman Bey.
But more importantly, what's Nikola's
goal on this marriage?
Nikola wants to marry Mari and strenghten
his ties with Kosses.
But we'll be more nimble.
We'll stop that.
By taking Mari, we'll hurt the lords.
And when Nikola can't find what he
expected, their relation will get hurt.
They'll lose their unity.
Taking Mari will separate them.
This will cause many good things.
I will give you my bravest alps.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Söğüt artisans are working
to deliver the goods.
Welcome, my sheik.
Thank you, Akça.
Dervish Akça.
He'll prepare the leather you want.
It's high quality.
Interesting.
There is no difference in quality.
How do you assure that?
Don't your masters ever
make bad crafts?
Firstly, the boots you liked...
is a gift from me to you.
And the answer to your question...
this is why we have the Ahi Order.
Firstly, we hire by competence.
Not even a single person who doesn't
deserve it can get the job.
They can't get approval.
All the masters are taught from
apprenticeship.
They are all given jobs according
to their competence.
But, the real thing is...
morals.
Our prophet, Hz.Muhammad...
peace be upon him...
was also a trader.
We follow him in trade,
as in everything else.
We work with his morals.
What are our goals, Akça Dervish?
Making good goods...
and selling them without
getting haram money.
Our only goal is to make
halal money.
Thank you.
That's why, Governor Saguros.
Like all the artisans, Akça makes
the best.
Not at all, my sheik.
We try our best.
Go to the woofer.
If you find one faulty good...
all his goods and money is yours.
Go to the tinner, if you find
one hole...
all his goods are a gift
from me to you.
Governor Saguros!
-My Sheik.
-Governor Saguros...
my bey wanted me to convey it.
Your rooms are ready.
You can rest until dinner.
No need for that.
Your word is the guarantee
of our trade.
-Thank you.
-Now, if you allow me...
I want to take some rest.
Have a nice day.
Come, please.
Damn it!
This thing will be over tonight.
Where are they now?
Osman is hosting a dinner at the inn for
Saguros this evening.
We will sneak into the inn.
We will get the men inside from there.
No one will escape.
What is your plan?
The kitchen.
We will go undercover and get the men
in from there.
Not only Saguros but also his daughter
will die.
This incident must be a big trouble
for Osman.
Good evening.
Here you go.
In the name of Allah, the compassionate,
the merciful.
O our Rabb, who spreads sustenance
to whom he wills without reckoning.
Thank you for your blessings.
-Amen.
O Almighty Rabb...
...grant us the opportunity to taste
these beauties...
...which you made us taste at this table,
in your eternal home, heaven.
Amen.
Grant us to be grateful for
these blessings...
...and to serve you.
Amen.
In the name of Allah, the compassionate,
the merciful.
Here you go.
In the name of Allah, the compassionate,
the merciful.
Come on.
You taught me a lot about archery today.
You are really good at it.
You were no less, Hera.
If you complete your practices
you will become a master too.
No!
Father!
Are you all right?
I am!
On my table, to my guests!
Who did this?
Alps!
Come on!
To the inn, to the Söğüt!
Spread everywhere!
You will find the traitors!
Come on, Alps!
Father! Are you okay, father!
- I am fine.
-You are fine!
Father!
The arrow can be poisonous.
Carry him to the room!
Come on!
-Father! Father!
-Come on!
-Father!
-To the room, come on!
-Göktuğ, Göktuğ!
-Göktuğ
My brother!
Father!
Baysungur!
They just wanted to cook some good
meal for Osman Bey.
But the traitors took their lives.
What is the positon?
They killed them, my Bey.
They wore their clothes.
Find a clue, a trace.
Check everywhere.
Of course, my Bey.
Kumral Abdal.
What is his position, tell us.
I gave him the antidote, my Bey.
But the poison is too strong.
No, no, no!
You are the most skilled healer!
Only you can heal him.
I hope, my Bey. I hope.
O Allah, the healer.
Father!
Hera.
Don't upset yourself.
Your father will recover.
I will hang at the door of Söğüt...
...whoever did this...
...at my inn, at my table, at Söğüt.
As soon as I get them.
Kumral Abdal...
...how is Göktuğ?
I gave him the antidote, my Bey.
He is next door.
What happened, Alps?
There was an attack but everyone is fine.
Don't worry.
-Is Osman Bey fine?
- He is.
No need to worry.
What is happening?
Damn it!
Didn't you succeed?
I am grateful to you.
If you weren't there maybe I would
too--
It is nothing.
Protecting you is my duty.
Are you all right?
I am.
Brother, are you all right?
I am fine, brother.
O Allah, the healer.
So your chest is hurting?
It doesn't Kumral Abdal.
It doesn't.
I am not talking about this.
I am talking about this.
Allah, Allah!
The secret is revealed, my Göktuğ!
You solved it!
Look at Osman Bey's valiants!
All of their wounds are bleeding
differently.
Various trials.
Love is a trial.
Sometimes you are trialed by separation...
... sometimes by unity.
Which lover came together with his lover
without a trial?
What if it is impossible?
There is no impossible love.
Listen to what I say.
But not with your ears...
...listen with your hearts, my valiants.
Look how crazy it beats!
In the time of the Prophet, there was
a lover companion named Suheyf.
He neither had a home nor money.
But this is love. It stuck in Suheyf's
heart like an arrow from a bow.
His heart beat saying ''love''.
Suheyf fell in love with the beautiful
Şifa Hatun.
Everybody wanted Şifa Hatun.
But she didn't love any of them.
All she wanted was Allah's blessing.
She asked the Prophet...
...''O Allah's Prophet...
... what should I do to get
Allah's blessing?''
Muhammad, whose name is also beautiful
said...
...''Şifa, the faith of the single man
is half...
...marry so that your faith will be
full.''
And Şifa said ''Then you choose whom
I will marry.''
Our Prophet said...
...I will marry you to the first person
who comes to the morning prayer tomorrow.
She was beautiful.
She had many candidates.
They put golds over her road.
They all slept with the wish of going
first in the morning.
Suheyf...
...didn't see himself as worthy for
Şifa Hatun.
He thought his love was impossible.
His heart beat saying ''Şifa!''.
But he didn't speak.
Didn't he go to the prayer?
He did go...
...but slowly.
Can someone escape his fate?
Could you?
None of the companions were
in love with Şifa Hatun...
...could wake up in the morning.
Despite of his slowness, Suheyf was the
first to enter the mosque.
Did he get his love?
He did!
Is what you see and Allah sees the same,
son?
What he saw as impossible was
his fate.
He walked slowly, took the long road.
But he got his love eventually.
The secret is solved!
did he get his love
Who can stand against love?
No one!
Thank you, Kumral Abdal.
Thank you.
The secret is solved.
The secret is solved!
Father!
Hera.
My girl.
Are you all right?
I am.
I am. You are too, Thank God!
Osman Bey.
Did you wait here for me?
I am grateful.
You saved...
...my...
...and my daughter's life.
Who kills and saves is Allah.
The bridge for this healing is
Kumral Abdal.
Anyway.
You rest now.
Father.
My girl.
Thank God you opened your eyes.
Thankfully...
...Saguros is fine.
He is alive.
But we weren't the target.
It was Saguros.
They were going to kill him and then
use that as an excuse to attack us.
Those who can't win in war
play games like this, my Bey.
Thus, we must always be cautious.
Brother, get the Alps ready for war.
We will go to İnegöl with Saguros.
But we will cross the border of İnegöl
with him without using our swords.
Then we will attack the mine.
My Alps are inside.
While they hurt the inside...
...we'll hurt the outside.
Just like a wolfpack.
As you order, my Bey!
Harmankaya Castle
Did you succeed?
The inn got messy, Kosses.
I couldn't even understand what happened.
Go on.
I was waiting outside.
Suddenly, Alps started to move.
I waited but my men didn't come out.
Saguros.
Osman's Alps started searching
all the Söğüt.
I had to run.
There is only one thing I wonder!
Is Saguros dead?
Or not?
Is Saguros dead or not?
He didn't!
Get out!
We came.
You gave us a great greeting and
honored us.
Now you gave the same delicacy for our
leave.
We couldn't let you go alone.
How?
My enemies do their business in secret.
I don't think they would dare to attack
openly.
They don't know where to stop.
But they know how to ambush well.
Don't forget about yesterday.
Thus, me and my Alps will accompany you.
Have you received ambush intelligence?
You're dressed like you're going
to war rather than a road.
Their ambush and their games are like
sand in the desert.
Because we are always on the alert
and always ready for war.
I am grateful to you, Soldier.
You saved my daughter's life.
Thank you. Anyone would do the same.
Your soldiers are like you, Osman Bey.
I am glad I made brave friends like you.
Thank you.
Don't be surprised at their courage.
Since they are not soldiers...
... they are Kayı Alps.
Alps!
Come on!
My beautiful sister.
I hope you will be so happy.
Nikola is a smart man.
I am sure he will make you very happy.
You always thought about me.
You always wanted the best for me.
I am grateful to you, brother.
I haven't seen you this happy for
a long time.
Why not?
Of course, I will be.
This is my sister's happiest day.
Come on.
Soldier!,
I don't want any problem.
Everything will be perfect.
All is as you wish, Sir.
The gifts were safely loaded into the car.
Get ready. We are leaving.
What if Turgut Bey can't make it?
If he can't come.
If I am lucky, Nikola will die...
... and if I am not, don't forget me,
Cornelia.
Sir, someone is coming!
This is Osman!
How dare you pass here, Osman?
We do not answer the dog.
Are we going to answer its tail?
Get out of my way!
Is there a problem?
I didn't know you were here, Sir.
Now you do. Open the road!
Inegöl Castle
It is very nice of you to send your tailor
for the wedding suit, Rogatus.
Thank you.
Do you think it will be ready on time?
Hmm?
He is not just the best tailor...
...he is also the fastest, Nikola.
It's done, Sir.
Good. Good.
There is also something bad.
Lord Saguros and his daughter
is still alive.
What?
How?
My men injured Saguros but couldn't
get out alive.
Damn it!
I will kill all of them myself!
Myself!
Since your clumsy men couldn't kill him...
...I'll be wearing battle armor,
not a wedding suit.
Get my armor!
You should've done it then!
They are coming, my Bey.
Let them.
Alps!
You know what to do!
Yes, my Bey!
My dear friend...
... am I stupid?
Would I marry for love like stupid
people?
Am I dumb?
Power, Rogatus!
Power!
More! More! More! More!
We have to be family for that.
Now you seem to have changed your mind.
Never!
No one can stop me from marrying Mari.
You should watch your words.
Rogatus...
...we need to take a break from this
fight.
For now.
Lord Saguros.
You will continue alone for the rest of
the road.
I have always been alone, Osman Bey.
Until I met you and your friends.
Thank you.
Have a nice trip.
But don't forget that...
... you are always welcomed in my tribe,
in my table.
As you say.
Thank you.
Mashallah!
I want to give you this so you can
continue to practice...
...in İznik.
You are very kind.
I hope we will see each other again.
I hope.
The Söğüt Market.
I can't wait to open it.
Those days are close.
But be careful on the road.
The caravan will have arrived before you.
Take care.
We hosted our friend.
Now we reached our goal.
Now...
...now it is time to conquer.
Let's go alps!
Ma'am, I think we arrived.
What if he is not here?
Jesus Christ.
Help us.
Turgut will come, Kornelia.
He won't leave me alone.
Mari.
Smile a bit, Mari.
You are marrying to a noble Lord.
Here we go.
Ambush!
Shield!
Mari stay behind me!
Forward!
Turgut!
Stop alps!
Damn it.
I am not going to kill you today, Kosses.
But I wouldn't move if I were you!
I'd stand there!
My archers will kill everyone who moves!
Whoever they are!
Turgut!
Are you crazy?
I am leaving. I told you not to force me!
What are you doing?
Never!
I will never let you go to a Turk!
Then kill me.
What is happening there?
Mair.
You can't do this to me, Mari.
You'll regret this.
Mari!
The marriage game is over, brother.
Alps!
What are you looking for?
Go after them!
Turgut Bey!
I have soldiers all around the forest!
You can't run away!
- Boran.
- My Bey.
Attack in the middle with alps.
Then meet our men inside.
As you order my Bey.
- Goktug.
- Yes my Bey.
You'll attack in the right side.
I'll be on the left.
Eyvallah (okay) my Bey.
It's time to slaughter!
However...
...we can't give any martyr.
Even one loss means defeat.
They can't get away.
Turgut!
I'll make a chalice out of your skull!
A chalice!
Hurry Nikola!
Seperate!
Come on my lions!
My Bey, leave.
We'll hold them.
Let's go Mari.
Sir, we found this.
This is Mari's dress.
Mari.
Smell, smell, come on.
Which way?
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on boy!
Come on!
Take us to them!
Let's go.
Alps.
The conquer of Inegol...
...starts in that mine.
May our war be holy.
Go!
Allah is eternal!
Attack alps!
Now!
The favor of the creator!
They are here brother.
- We shall begin then.
- We do, brother.
They are catching up!
Where are we supposed to go in this
huge forest?
Calm down.
I'll not let them hurt you.
Let's go.
They are catching up.
Let them catch up.
I thought of something.
Get in.
Check everywhere!
Everywhere!
Get away from there!
I found you Turgut!
Soldier!
I found you!
I'll let those wolves who you love
so much eat you!
I'll make a chalice out of your skull!
I will drink your blood with it!
Hold on.
Nikola, Mari.
Mari is mine!
She is mine!
Give it to me, brother!
Hay Masha Allah! (praise be)
Masha Allah(praise be) my valiants!
Thank Allah my Bey.
Thank Allah.
We shall meet our valiant alps...
who paved the way for...
...this victory.
They have men in the mine, Lord!
We should leave.
Osman claimed the mine!
We are not waiting in vain, Julia.
Sir.
Osman will attack the mine.
What's your plan?
I will have a great surprise for him,
Rogatus.
At the moment he enters that mine...
The field will be hell!
I will be at the wedding, as you know...
...so this pleasure...
...will be yours to watch, Rogatus.
Osman will not get out of there!
So these tunnels will blow!
This is great news!
Now...
Come on!
Allah-u Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
Now!
Come on!
My heart burns!
Protect us, our Rab(Allah)
Alps!
Wait a bit.
Come on!
No.
Once my Bey conquers the mine...
...I will forge the best catapults!
I will forge the best cannonballs!
They will hit
Inegol Castle fast and furious!
Inshallah(if Allah permits)
Davut Agha.
Kumral Abdal, check that out.
Two catapults will shoot from here.
Two will shoot from right here.
And three catapults will shoot from here.
Then the feast will start!
You just destroy.
Hit there!
Destroyed here!
You'll crash down the castle!
What will my Bey own then?
Davut Agha.
The thing is taking it in one piece.
Not destroying the whole meal.
Debris is not useful.
The thing is to have it in one piece
if possible, Master Davut.
Kumral Abdal, repelling an attack coming
from only one point is easy.
We'll lose many alps.
Is the building more important than
our lives?
Just keep being a saint!
You have no place in war!
You are wasting!
You'll have to repair all those walls!
I will do it!
As long as we conquer Inegol.
Inegol is nothing!
It is nothing for us!
We are going to have the
whole world, Davut Agha! The universe!
All is our homeland, all is ours!
Allah Allah!
Kumral Abdal, what's it?
I felt it.
I felt something.
There's something wrong.
My Allah, protect us.
My Bey!
Alps.
Alps!
My alps!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com